&gt;&gt; Here, you're going to learn how to use one of
&gt;&gt; ここで 学習するのは 自動運転車の開発で
the most exciting tools and self-driving car development, deep neural networks.
最も面白いツールの 1つである 深層ニューラルネットワークです
At the end of this module,
このモジュールの最後では
you'll create a project that demonstrates
皆さんに 自分で プロジェクトを作成し
real world application of the skills you need to become a self-driving car engineer.
自動運転車エンジニアに 求められるスキルを 示してもらいます
&gt;&gt; That's right. In the project you'll train
&gt;&gt; そのとおりです深層ニューラルネットワークを 学習させ
a deep neural network to drive a car in a simulator.
シミュレーターで 自動車を操縦させる プロジェクトでは
First, you'll drive and record training laps in simulation and then
まず あなたが シミュレーターで運転し 走行を記録します
you'll build and train a deep neural network that learns from the way you drive.
それから 深層ニューラルネットワークを 構築し あなたの運転の仕方を 学習させます
&gt;&gt; A deep neural network is just a term that describes a big multi-layer neural network.
&gt;&gt; 深層ニューラルネットワークとは 大規模な多層構造の ニューラルネットワークを 指すに過ぎません
&gt;&gt; And a neural network is
&gt;&gt; ニューラルネットワークという
a machine learning algorithm that you can train using input like
マシーンラーニングアルゴリズムは カメラ画像や センサー測定値といった
camera images or sensor readings and generate
入力を 使って 学習し
output like what's steering angle the car should take or how fast it should go.
車のステアリング角度や 走行速度といった 出力を 生成します
The idea is that the neural network learns from observing the world.
ニューラルネットワークの コンセプトは 観測からの学習です
You don't have to teach it anything specific.
具体的なことを 教える必要はありません
&gt;&gt; Deep learning is just another term for using deep neural networks to
&gt;&gt; ディープラーニングとは 深層ニューラルネットワークを 使った
solve problems and it's become really important for self-driving cars.
問題解決であり 自動運転車の分野で 重要な意味を 持ちます
&gt;&gt; But deep learning is relatively new.
&gt;&gt; しかし ディープラーニングは まだ新しい考え方です
Until the last few years,
つい最近まで
computers simply weren't fast enough to train deep neural networks effectively.
深層ニューラルネットワークを 効果的に学習させるには コンピューターの速度が 足りなかったのです
Now, however, automotive manufacturers can
しかし 今では 自動車メーカーが
apply deep learning techniques to drive cars in real time.
ディープラーニング技術を使って 自動車をリアルタイムで 運転できるように なりました
&gt;&gt; Because deep learning is so new,
&gt;&gt; ディープラーニングは 新しい技術なので
automotive engineers and researchers are
自動車エンジニアや 研究者たちは
still experimenting with just how far it can take us,
何が可能なのかを 実験しているところです
but deep learning has already revolutionized segments of autonomous driving like
しかし ディープラーニングは すでにコンピュータービジョンのような
computer vision and it has the potential to
分野で 革命を起こしており
entirely change the way we develop self-driving cars.
自動運転車の開発方法を がらりと 変えてしまう力を 秘めています